https://pestcontrolamerica.com/privacy-policy/

Loading... Please wait...
My Account
Sign in or Create an account
Currency Displayed in
Wish Lists
View Cart (0)
Manufacturers
Gardner Bayer Enviromental BASF Protect-A-Bed Zoecon BASF - VECTOR Bell Labs Whitmire Catchmaster Dupont
View All Brands
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
Pest Control America Privacy Statement: We are highly sensitive to the privacy interests of consumers and believe that the protection of those interests is one of our most significant responsibilities. In acknowledgment of our obligations, we have adopted the following Privacy Policy applicable to information about consumers that we acquire in the course of our day to day business activities.
Acquisition of Information: We do not acquire any more information about consumers than is required by law or is otherwise necessary to provide a high level of service efficiently and securely.
Our Employees and Privacy: We train all of our employees about the importance of privacy. We give access to information about consumers only to those employees who require it to perform their jobs.
Security Measures: We make access to privacy-sensitive information subject to rigorous procedural and technological controls, consistent with legal requirements and the demands of customer service.
Disclosure to Third Parties: We will provide individually-identifiable information about consumers to third parties only as is necessary to process transactions and provide UPS or USPS shipping services.
Privacy and Third Parties: When we make our technology or services available to any third party as required to process business transactions, we will not share with them any more consumer information than is absolutely necessary, and we will always make every reasonable effort to assure, by contract or otherwise, that these third parties use our technology and services in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Policy.
Our Featured Products
Mantis Fly Light - 2X2
$322.95
Add to Compare
Add to Wishlist
Add To Cart
Vector Plasma One Screened Fly Light
$189.95
| Copyright 2020 Pest Control America. All Rights Reserved.
Sitemap |
All prices are in USD.
Close
Close
Selected For Comparision
Compare Now
